Guide to the Corcoran Gallery of Art and Corcoran College of Art + Design,Corcoran Gallery of Art education department records 1961-2010 COR0006.0.RG
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Programs files [2016 processing project], 2003-2013; Series 20
  - Healy Cordeiro, 2011 December 1; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 40)
  - Paatterns in Creativity, 2011 December 7; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 41)
  - Bert Ulrich Jim Dean NASA Art Program, 2011 December 6; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 42)
  - Designs on Film, 2011 December 8; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 43)
  - Norway Fashion, 2011; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 44)
  - Barkely Hendricks Trevor, 2012 January 19; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 45)
  - Nick Cave, 2012 January 26; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 46)
  - 30 Americans Symposium, Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 47)
  - William Pope L., 2012 February 1; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 48)
  - Xaviera Simmons, 2012 February 8; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 49)
  - Verge, 2012 Marchh 18; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 50)
  - Walker Kara, 2012 February 6; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 51)
  - EFF: Michelle Oka Doner, 2012 March 21; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 52)
  - Deadline Every Second, 2012 March 22; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 53)
  - Jefferson Pinder: Ben-Hur, 2012 March 22; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 54)
  - Gray Performance, 2012 March 25; Series 20 (Box 68, Folder 55)
  - Tour with Andy at Smithsonian American Art Museum (SAAM), 2012 April 11; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 1)
  - Grad Symposium, 2012 April 22; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 2)
  - Campion Platt, 2012 May 2; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 3)
  - Tim Hetherington Panel, 2012 May 7; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 4)
  - Brown Davis Interior Design, 2012 May 8; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 5)
  - Meet the Corcoran's Next Artists, 2012 May 10; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 6)
  - Where Soldiers Come From, 2012 May 17; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 7)
  - Jonathan Adler, 2012 May; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 8)
  - Arts The Military, 2012 May 28; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 9)
  - Emerging Arts Lenders Panel, 2012 June; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 10)
  - Isabel Toledo Robin Givhan, 2012 June 14; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 11)
  - Sperryville Tour, 2012 June; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 12)
  - Discovering Diebenkorn, 2012 June 28; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 13)
  - Yoga on the Bridge, 2012 July 7 - 2012 July 21; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 14)
  - FSS: Beach Bums, 2012 July 7; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 15)
  - Words Beats Life (FSS Performance), 2012 July 14; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 16)
  - Voices of Haiti, 2012 July; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 17)
  - ESA Nickle, 2012 August 9; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Armed Programming, 2012 August 30; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 19)
  - John Cage Festival Opening, 2012 September 4; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 20)
  - First Cameraman Arun Chauhary, 2012 September 5; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 21)
  - Gretchen Diebenkorn Grant, 2012 September 13; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 22)
  - Poetics of Place Poetry Reading, 2012 September 20; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 23)
  - Verge, 2012 September 23; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 24)
  - What a Relief: Family Workshop, 2010 August 14; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 25)
  - Cosmo Couoture, 2012 September 27; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 26)
  - Community, 2012 October; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 27)
  - Bridge Performance Panel, 2012 October 11; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 28)
  - Charlotte Dumas Visiting Artist, 2012 October 18; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 29)
  - Cameron Silver, 2012 October; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 30)
  - Dressed to Dance, 2012 October; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 31)
  - Ivan Sigal, 2012 November 12; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 32)
  - Sofia Taboas Eduardo Abaroa, 2012 November 15; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 33)
  - Silk Painting Workshop, 2012 November 17; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 34)
  - Taryn Simon Newman Lecture, 2012 November 8; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 35)
  - Reporters Without Borders/Magnum, 2012 November 14; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 36)
  - Enoc Perez Visiting Artists, 2012 November 26; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 37)
  - United in Anger, 2012 December 4; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 38)
  - Write Home Soon, 2012 December 15; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 39)
  - Yoga, 2013 January 5 - 2013 January 26; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 40)
  - Mobile Movie Film Festival, 2013 January 19; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 41)
  - Create at the Corcoran Happy Hour, 2013 January 23; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 42)
  - Mobile Museum Artist Conference, 2013 January 26; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 43)
  - Andrea Fraser Visiting Artist, 2013 January 28; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 44)
  - Allen Ellenzweig The Homorerotic Photograph, 2013 February 7; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 45)
  - Book Making Workshop, 2013 February 20; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 46)
  - Roger Gastman, 2013 February 27; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 47)
  - Pump Me Up Panel, 2013 March 12; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 48)
  - Shodekeh, 2013 March 13; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 49)
  - Kip Lornel, 2013 March; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 50)
  - EFF: Bending Sticks (Patrick Dougherty), 2013 March 19; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 51)
  - Globe Poster Gallery Talk, 2013 March 27; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 52)
  - Verge, 2013 March; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 53)
  - Legend of Cool Disco Dan, 2013 March 27; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 54)
  - Pump Me Up Panel, 2013 March 28; Series 20 (Box 69, Folder 55)
- Tours, interns, publicity files [2016 processing project], 1971-2000; Series 21
  Immediate Source of Acquisition
  The materials housed in box 70 are the records for Accession 2016.111 donated in 2016 by Vivian Brodsky.
  - Carey, Janis, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Kirk, Christina, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Donnelly, Lisa Ann, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - Parker, Shalon, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - Lloyd, Donna, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - College Summer Intern positions 1992, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - Loose Correspondence, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Dennis, Karen, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Leisure and Labor, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Corcoran Exhibits, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - FH Tour Schedules, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Allison Knight Development, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Sarah Kuffler Education, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Jennifer Tunny Registrar, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Samantha Newcom Public Affairs, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Karen Luik, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Interns, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Elisa Dugundji Prints & Drawings, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Adriana Bourgoin Development, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Interns-Summer 1991 Sarah Morgon Prints & Drawings, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Intern Time Sheets Summer 1992, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Package Check Form, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - School Without Walls Jr. Guards Songs of My People, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - Intern - Info., Reports, Procedures, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - Minority Internship 1990, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Minority Internship 1991, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - Interns: Summer 1989 Miscellaneous Memos, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Internship, Programs, Applications, Previous, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Minority Interrnship 1992, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Letters, Correspondence, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Carol Cadby Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Sharon Carman Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Lisa Kapp Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Leslie Kirkby Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Carolyn Kuntz Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - Robert Lawrence Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Diana Linden Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Karen Porterfield Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - Sarah Sabiston Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Liz triplett Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Summer Interns: General, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Summer Interns 1983 General Stuff, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Summer Interns Final Reports 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 43)
  - Tri-Weekly Reports 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 44)
  - Robyn Asleson Intern Summer, 1983, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 45)
  - Summer Interns 1982 General, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 46)
  - Memos Typed, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - Summer Intern Applicants, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 48)
  - Summer Inntern Applicants, 1983-1984; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 49)
  - Nancy Eickel, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 50)
  - Out-Of-Garey Sessions 1981 Summer Interns, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 51)
  - 1982 Summer Intern Final Reports, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 52)
  - Out-Of-Gallery Sessions 1982, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - Out-Of-Gallery Session Evaluation, 1981; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 54)
  - Loose Documents, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 55)
  - Loose Documents, circa 1981-1991; Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 56)
  - Summer Interns 1982 Housing, Series 21 (Box 15, Folder 57)
  - Art & Youth CGA, 1971 June 6 - July 19; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 1)
  - High School Show 1971 Docent Materials, Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 2)
  - Washington Art Series April 1974, 1974 April; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 3)
  - Washington Art Series Oct./Nov. 74, 1974 October-November; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 4)
  - Architecture: Discovery & Awareness Handbook--Extras, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 5)
  - American Litthographs Corcoran Permanent Collection, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 6)
  - American Art in the Making Text and List of Exhibited Works, 1977 January; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 7)
  - Women at the Corcoran: Pttngs. of Women in the American Collection, 1976 December 1; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 8)
  - Discover CGA, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 9)
  - CGA "Made in America" Packet, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 10)
  - Armand Hammer Collection Packets, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 11)
  - Architecture is Elementary, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 12)
  - Docents Manual 1972-73, 1972-1973; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 13)
  - CGA Education Dept. Washington Art Readings, 1970; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 14)
  - (Ed. Dept.) Summer / Weekend Workshops, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 15)
  - Educ. Dpt.: Misc. Literature, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 16)
  - First National Bank - Chicago, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 17)
  - Inaugural Activities, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 18)
  - CGA Board of Trustees, 1980 July; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 19)
  - Corcoran Shop, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 20)
  - Lectures + Wed. Gallery Talks, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 21)
  - Tours RE: Specific Shows, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 22)
  - Listing of Current Exhibits, 1972-1980; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 23)
  - Misc. Educ. Tours Offered, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 24)
  - CGA Summer Intern Handbook, 1977; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 25)
  - Loose Packets and Papers, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 26)
  - Brackets/Studio Four, HY Myers/Lighting/Molding, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 27)
  - Socles/Expenses, P.O.S. Budgets/Paint/Columns, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 28)
  - Pedestals/Glass/Miscellaneous, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 29)
  - Grills/Photographs (Xeroxed Photos) Design Issues, Circa 1971-1989; Series 21 (Box 18, Folder 30)
  - Elizabeth Burr, Circa 1993-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 1)
  - Kerri Echardt Spring 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 2)
  - Aubrey Alter Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 3)
  - Stone Ridge Interns, Circa 1993-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 4)
  - Tania Said, Circa 1993-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 5)
  - Reagan Kiser GW Museum Education Spring 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 6)
  - Donna Gesualdo GW Museum Education Spring 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 7)
  - Jason Brantley, Circa 1993-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 8)
  - Laura Jacobs Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 9)
  - Mauricio Herrero Spring 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 10)
  - Capera Ryan Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 11)
  - Cara Kroenke Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 12)
  - Jennifer Kaufman Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 13)
  - Carrie Loud Ssummer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 14)
  - Jennifer Robinson Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 15)
  - Adina Loeb Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 16)
  - Melanie Weeks Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 17)
  - Jennifer Horning Fall 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 18)
  - Alison Frost Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 19)
  - Stephen Baer Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 20)
  - Interns 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 21)
  - Katherine Climo Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 22)
  - Kimberly Grossman 1996-97, 1996-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 23)
  - Daphne Liu Fall 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 24)
  - Dara Sicherman Summer 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 25)
  - Jacqueline Liu Summer 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 26)
  - Tracy Pottkery-Fishel Summer 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 27)
  - Alejandra Jimenez Summer 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 28)
  - David Hershey Summer 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 29)
  - Ann Maier Spring 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 30)
  - Mona Khademi Intern Fall 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 31)
  - Sien OhGW Museum Ed. Intern, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 32)
  - Field School Interns Jessica Fleres & Rebecca Mann Jan/Feb 1996, 1996 January-February; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 33)
  - Laura Yaggy Summer 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 34)
  - Lee Anne Gardner-Warrenfell Summer 1996, Circa 1993-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 35)
  - Intern memos 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 36)
  - Lisa Chow, 1995; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 37)
  - Christina Segovia Intern-Fall 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 38)
  - Jennifer Culp Intern Summer 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 39)
  - Etienne Hellman, 1995; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 40)
  - Erica Wiekhardt Intern Summer 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 41)
  - Sarah Craighiill Intern Summer 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 42)
  - Laura Hicks Intern Summer 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 43)
  - Roopal Patel Intern Summer 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 44)
  - Kyra Jablonsky Post grad intern spring 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 45)
  - Sybil Keats-Bjorksten Intern-Spring 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 46)
  - Kristy Jamrisko 3/95 one-day mentorship, 1995 March; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 47)
  - Blanquita Cullum Undergrad Intern - March 1995, 1995 March; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 48)
  - Robin emanali High School Intern - May 1995, 1995 May; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 49)
  - Tim Scott High School intern - Jan. 1995, 1995 January; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 50)
  - Christina Lleras High School Intern - May 1995, 1995 May; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 51)
  - Christopher Reddaway High School Intern - Jan 1995, 1995 January; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 52)
  - Chris Martin High School Intern - Fall 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 53)
  - Liz Satterlee High School Intern 1993 - 1995, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 54)
  - Julia Smith, 1995-1996; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 55)
  - Lisa Charde Intern Fall 1995, Circa 1993-1997; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 56)
  - Rhonda Howard Graduate intern Fall 94 - Spring 1995, 1994-1995; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 57)
  - Julie Joyce Graduate intern Fall 1994 - Spring 1995, 1994-1995; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 58)
  - Sher King Pst-Grad Intern - Fall 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 59)
  - Suzanne Swanson Interrn Summer 1994, 1994 February-August; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 60)
  - George Kimmerling Intern Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 61)
  - Carolyn Saunders Intern Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 62)
  - John Orr Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 63)
  - Ben Shaykin 1994 - Summer, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 64)
  - Pascal Spengemann Intern Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 65)
  - Vanessa York Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 66)
  - Silvina Fernandez-Duque Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 67)
  - Laura Gomez Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 68)
  - Michelle Saffir Graduate inter Fall 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 69)
  - Jill Thompson Undergrad intern - Fall 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 70)
  - Cynthia Carter Post-grad intern Fall 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 71)
  - Maria Villafane Undergrad intern - Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 72)
  - Sarah Heim Johnson UVA Extern - May 1994, 1994 May; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 73)
  - Leila Kawar HS Intern Spring 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 74)
  - Kristen Buck - Spring 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 75)
  - Aaron Mendelsohn Intern Summer 1994, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 76)
  - Christine Mulligan Post-grad Fall 93 Spring 94, 1993-1994; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 77)
  - Katie O'Neill Intern Summere 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 78)
  - Eshelle Williams Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 79)
  - Kristen Poopp Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 80)
  - Donna Weir Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 81)
  - Yvonne Garcia Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 82)
  - Christin Tierney Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 83)
  - Shahin Yayha Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 84)
  - Ali Salaverria Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 85)
  - Cricket Henize Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 86)
  - Sheila Weiss Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 87)
  - Laura Nova Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 88)
  - Ruth Vianna Intern Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 89)
  - Margaret Wilkerson Interrn Summer 1993, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 90)
  - CGA Summer Intern Program 1993 - Packet, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 91)
  - CGA 1995 Summer Intern Handbook, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 92)
  - CGA Summer Interns Packet 1982, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 93)
  - CGA Summer Interns Packet 1983, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 94)
  - CGA Summer Interns Packet 1981, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 95)
  - Summer Internship 1996, Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 96)
  - GW Museum Education Interns Applicants, 1994 April-October; Series 21 (Box 20, Folder 97)
  - CGA Summer Intern Handbook, 1977 June-; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 1)
  - Interns 93, 1993; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 2)
  - Interns 94, 1994; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 3)
  - Out of Gallery Trips 1994, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 4)
  - Interns 1995, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 5)
  - Interns/ 1996, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 6)
  - Very Special Arts interns Robert Major & Robert Lewis Summer 1997, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 7)
  - Kari Sullivan Fall 1997, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 8)
  - Renee Ater Fall 1997 - Spring 1998, 1997-1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 9)
  - Sharon Appel Fall 1997 - Spring 1998, 1997-1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 10)
  - Elizabeth Botten January 1998, 1998 January; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 11)
  - Colleen Harris January 1998, 1998 January; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 12)
  - Ariane Weisel February 1998, 1998 February; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 13)
  - Jennifer Brown Spring Semester 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 14)
  - Rebecca Lemmon Spring 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 15)
  - Velica Steadman Spring 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 16)
  - Aaron Rich Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 17)
  - Jana Henning Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 18)
  - Deborah Stengle Spring Semester 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 19)
  - Rebeca Gonzalez Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 20)
  - Nami Fujimoto Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 21)
  - Kate Cunningham Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 22)
  - Abigail Fojas Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 23)
  - Ingrid Flautt Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 24)
  - Sondra Fein Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 25)
  - Mary Spencer Craddock Summer 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 26)
  - Summer Internship Program 1998, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 27)
  - Fall '98 Internship Jody Rosen, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 28)
  - Fall '98 Internship Christine Hopper, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 29)
  - Fall '98 Internship Stephanie Hilliard, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 30)
  - Fall '98 Internship Pilar Loizaga, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 31)
  - Fall '98 Internship Annaliese Cassarino, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 32)
  - Fall '98 Internship Jennifer Sherlock, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 33)
  - Fall '98 Internship Alice Mallet, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 34)
  - Fall '98 Internship Isis Johnson, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 35)
  - Fall '98 Internship Andra Eglitis, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 36)
  - Fall '98 Internship Mica Scalin, 1998; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 37)
  - Department Request Interns Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 38)
  - Intern Program Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 39)
  - Interns 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 40)
  - Christine Hopper GWU Mus Ed 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 41)
  - Summer Interns, 1999; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 42)
  - Jovana Joyner, 1999; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 43)
  - Carol Ann Small Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 44)
  - Megan Hearn Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 45)
  - Mark Edward Best Intern Appplicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 46)
  - Divya Rao Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 47)
  - Payal S. Parekh Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 48)
  - Renata Szalovska Baginski Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 49)
  - Marget Van Horn Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 50)
  - Marisa Jill Leshinsky Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 51)
  - Ariana Markoe Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 52)
  - Gayle Horn Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 53)
  - Jennifer Lynn Lamping Intern Applicant Summer 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 54)
  - Melanie Eisna Fall 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 55)
  - Robyn Weinstein Fall 1999, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 56)
  - Ruth Cady Tenny Winter 2000 (Jam), Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 57)
  - Adrian Redmond Madeira Intern - 1999-2000, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 58)
  - Chris Dubia - Paul + Philip CCAD Fall 1999 - Spring 2000, 1999-2000; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 59)
  - Anthony Utley VACOP Mentorship - Fall 1999 Spring 2000, 1999-2000; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 60)
  - Karen Daley GWU - Spring 2000, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 61)
  - Maggie Glebes May 2000, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 62)
  - Julia Galef HS Intern - Summer 2000, Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 63)
  - Katherine Osterman, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 64)
  - Leta O'steen, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 65)
  - Jennifer O'Keefe, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 66)
  - Elizabeth Varghese, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 67)
  - Jennifer Colaguori, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 68)
  - Dayal S. Parekh, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 69)
  - Kathryn Ward, Circa 1993-2001; Series 21 (Box 21, Folder 70)